tolmolbol.com 2011-06-01

# Privacy Policy | tolmolbol

|  |  |   
---  
| Privacy Policy  
---  
tolmolbol is an online application that helps you reach out to your locality and find information about your friends, businesses, events, classifieds and local favourites. We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting your personal information.  
Personal Information

tolmolbol asks for some personal information when you sign-up, including your email address and a password. By registering yourself, you will be able to access many services that require sign-up. As a tolmolbol member you can create an account based on your name, age, gender, hometown, interests, occupation, photos, gender and any other content. This information is voluntary and may be available to other users. 

Your name will be associated with your posts, reviews and messages. Additionally, your name and email address may be included in the messages, compliments, friendship requests or invitations you send to other users. When you invite new members or send messages through tolmolbol, we may collect and maintain information associated with those messages, including email addresses and content.

Further, we may also log your browser-type related information, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp. This will help us diagnose problems and provide the best level of service to you. In addition, we will be able to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the site.  
  
Links

Our website may contain links to third party websites. We encourage you to read the privacy polices on these websites as we are not responsible for their respective privacy practices.

go to top  
  
Security We restrict access to your information to authorized personnel only and we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of your information. However, transmissions made by means of the internet cannot be made absolutely secure. By using this site, you agree that we will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties. 

go to top  
  
In the Event of Merger or Sale

In the event that tolmolbol is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control.

go to top  
  
Contact Information

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, please send us an email to [info@tolmolbol.com](mailto:info@tolmolbol.com)

go to top  
  
Policy ChangesThe effective date of this policy is January 1, 2007. We reserve the right to change or update this policy at any time. Such changes shall be effective immediately upon posting to this site. You are responsible for reviewing this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes to it. Your continued use of the site indicates your assent to any changes to this Privacy Policy.

go to top
